hithere.com 2013-05-08

# Privacy policy | HiThere - World Leading Webgame Developer and Operator

Your privacy is critically important to us. At HiThere we have a few fundamental principles: 

● We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.

● We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact our customer service team. It is Hithere’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals: 

###  Website Visitors 

Like most websites, HiThere collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. HiThere’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how HiThere’s visitors use its website. From time to time, HiThere may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. HiThere also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. HiThere only discloses logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below. 

###  Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information 

Certain visitors to HiThere choose to interact with HiThere in ways that require HiThere to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that HiThere gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask players who sign up to play our games to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in monetary transactions with HiThere – by purchasing “HiThere Points” – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, HiThere collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with HiThere. HiThere does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

###  Aggregated Statistics 

HiThere may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. HiThere may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, HiThere does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below 

###  Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information 

HiThere discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on HiThere’s behalf or to provide services available at HiThere’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using HiThere’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. HiThere will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, HiThere discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when HiThere believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of HiThere, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of HiThere and have supplied your email address, HiThere may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with HiThere and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. HiThere takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

###  Cookies 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. HiThere uses cookies to help HiThere identify and track visitors, their usage of HiThere website, and their website access preferences. HiThere visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using HiThere’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of HiThere’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

###  Business Transfers 

If HiThere, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that HiThere goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of HiThere may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

###  Forums 

As the forums are visible to the public please be aware that anything you write on the forum can and most likely will be seen by users you weren’t expecting to see what you wrote at the time you wrote it. 

###  Privacy Policy Changes 

Although most changes are likely to be minor, HiThere may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in HiThere’s sole discretion. HiThere encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
